Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education (SUPCE) Records
- Publications
  - Eric Clearinghouse on Adult Education series (ECA)
    - ECA36 [MISSING] Adult Education Research Current Information Series, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA37 [MISSING] ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA38 [MISSING] ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA39 [MISSING] Scope and Service of ERIC-AE, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA40 ERIC-AE Publications 1967-69, 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA41 [MISSING] Joint Newsletter with University College, Syracuse University Eric Clearinghouse on Adult Education (Box 8)
    - ECA42 Continuing Education for Adults (Nos. 129-154, 155, 157, 163, 166, 167, 171, 177, 179), 1968-1973 (Box 8)
    - ECA43 Research and Investigation in Adult Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA44 Evening College Education, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA45 Adult Education Periodical Holdings Literature, 1967 (Box 8)
    - ECA46 Abstracts of Papers Presented to the National Seminar on Adult Education Research, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA47 A Model Information System for the Adult Education Profession (DeCrow, Roger), 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA48 [MISSING] Cross-Cultural Training (DeCrow, Roger), 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA49 Mass Media in Adult Education: A Review of Recent Literature (Ohliger, John), 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA50 A Register of Research and Investigation in Adult Education Adult Education, 1968 (Box 8)
    - ECA51 Cross-Cultural Interaction Skills: A Digest of Recent Training (DeCrow, Roger), 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA52 Adult Education and the Disadvantaged Adult (Anderson, Darrell and Niemi, John A.), 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA53 Adult Education in Germany: Bibliography (Schadt, Armin L.), 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA54 [MISSING] A Handbook for Teachers of English to Non-English Speaking Adults (Hefferman-Cabrera, Patricia), 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA55 [MISSING] Adult Learning and Instruction (Grabowski, Stanley M., ed.), 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA56 Education for Aging: A Review of Recent Literature (Jacobs, H. Lee; Mason, W. Dean; Kauffman, Earl), 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA57 [MISSING] Correspondence Study: A Summary Review of the Research and, Development of Literature (Mathieson, David E.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA58 Self Concept in Adult Participation: Conference Report and Bibliography, 1969 (Box 8)
    - ECA59 [MISSING] The Use of Mass Media in Religiously Motivated Adult Educators: A Review of the Literature (Clyde, Robert W. Jaberg, Eugene C.), 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA60 Mass Media in Public Affairs: A Review of the Literature (Power, Hilton M.) (Box 8)
    - ECA61 Digests of Papers Presented to the Adult Research Conference, February 27-28, 1970 Minneapolis (Box 8)
    - ECA62 ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education: Publications,1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA63 [MISSING] ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education Information Analysis Priorities, 1970 (Box 8)
    - ECA64 [MISSING] The Mass Media in Cooperative Extension: A Review of Recent Literature (Everly, Jack C.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA65 [MISSING] Television: A Viable Channel for Educating Adults in Culturally Different Poverty Groups: A Literature Review (Niemi, John A. and Anderson, Darrel V.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA66 [MISSING] The Use of Mass Media in Adult Education in Countries Outside the U.S. and Canada: A Literature Review (Cassirer, Henry R.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA67 "I'm Beginning to Think Like the Bird!" Or, Social and Philosophical Issues in the Use of Mass Media in Adult Education: A Review of the Literature (Blakely, Robert J.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA68 [MISSING] The Mass Media in Adult Education in the Developing Countries: A Literature Review (Guevlette, David G.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA69 Cost Benefit Analysis and the Adult Educator: A Literature Review (Steele, Sara M.), 1971 (Box 8)
    - ECA70 Abstract of Papers Presented to the National Seminar on Adult Education Research February 1969, Toronto (Grabowski, Stanley M.) (Box 8)
    - ECA71 [MISSING] Needed: A New Coalition for Public Affairs Education (A Review of the Literature) (Johnson, Eugene I.), 1972 (Box 8)
    - ECA72 The Education of the Mentally Retarded Adult: A Selective Review of the Literature (Long, Huey B.), 1973 (Box 8)
    - ECA73 The Preparation of Adult Educators: A Selected Review of the Literature Produced in North America (Box 8)
  - Fund for Adult Education series (FAE)
    - FAE1 [MISSING] Economic Reasoning, An Introduction to (Robinson, Marshall A. and Morton, Herbert C.), 1955 (Box 10)
    - FAE2 Readings for the Executive Seminar, 2d edition (Brooks, Shepherd), 1960; Vol. I, Vol. II (Box 10)
    - FAE3 An Introduction to Economic Reasoning: A Manual for Discussion Group Participants and Leaders (Robinson, Marshall A. and Morton, Herbert C.), 1955 (Box 10)
    - FAE4 An Introduction to Economic Reasoning: Book of Readings (Robinson, Marshall A.; Morton, Herbert C.; Calderwood, James D.), 1956 (Box 10)
    - FAE5 Looking at Modern Painting: A Discussion Leader's Guide (Field, Frances) (Box 10)
    - FAE6 Looking at Modern Painting: A Study Discussion Program (Department of Art - University Extension - University of California, L.A.), 1957 (Box 10)
    - FAE7 An Introduction to the Humanities: A Guide for Discussion Leaders (Humanities Staff University of Chicago), 1958 (Box 10)
    - FAE8 What to Listen for in Music (Copland, Aaron), 1939 (Box 10)
    - FAE9 An Introduction to the Humanities: Book of Readings and Music Supplement (University of Chicago), 1955 (Box 10)
    - FAE10 Humanities: Adult Education Series: 10 Units Introducing Painting, Music and Literature, Revised (Ashbrook, William; Carpenter, Marjorie; Dudley, Louise; Sterling, Alfred), 1954 (Box 10)
    - FAE11 FAE Avenue to the Arts A. Authors - Biographical Sketch - Titles (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE12 FAE Avenue to the Arts B. Table of Contents (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE13 FAE Avenue to the Arts C. Part one - Part two (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE14 FAE Avenue to the Arts D. Part three - Session IV (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE15 FAE Avenue to the Arts E. Part three - Session V (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE16 FAE Avenue to the Arts F. Part three - Session VI (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE17 FAE Avenue to the Arts G. Part three - Session VII & VIII (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE18 FAE Avenue to the Arts H. Part three - Session IX (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE19 FAE Avenue to the Arts I. Part four - Session X (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE20 FAE Avenue to the Arts J. Part four - Session X & XI (Fund for Adult Education), 1959 (Box 10)
    - FAE21 The Educational Experience (Redfield, Robert), 1955 (Box 10)
    - FAE22 A Study of Participants in the Great Books Program (Davis, James A.), 1957 (Box 10)
    - FAE23 The Great Awakening: Including a Plan for Education for Leadership in the U.S. (Fletcher, C. Scott), 1958 (Box 10)
    - FAE24 Education for Public Responsibility (Fund for Adult Education), 1958 (Box 10)
    - FAE25 Accent on Learning (Burch, Glen), 1960 (Box 10)
    - FAE26 A Comparative Study of Lecture and Discussion Methods (Hill, Richard J.), 1960 (Box 10)
    - FAE27 Studies in Adult Group Learning in the Liberal Arts (Kaplan, Abbott), 1960 (Box 10)
    - FAE28 Able People Well Prepared (Shilen, Ronald), 1961 (Box 10)
    - FAE29 A Ten Year Report of the Fund for Adult Education 1951-1961: Ford Foundation (Box 10)
    - FAE30 [MISSING] Great Issues in American Politics: Part I (Hofstadter, Richard), 1956 (Box 10)
    - FAE31 [MISSING] The Happy Republic (Box 10)
    - FAE32 Readings in the Ways of Mankind Vol. 1, Vol. 2 (Fund for Adult Education), 1957 (Box 10)
    - FAE33 Readings in the Ways of Mankind: Discussion Leader's Guide, 1957 (Box 11)
    - FAE34 Looking at Modern Poetry (Freedman, Leonard, ed.), 1961 (Box 11)
    - FAE34A Discovering Modern Poetry (Drew, Elizabeth and Connor, George), 1961 (Box 11)
    - FAE34B Discovering Modern Poetry (Drew, Elizabeth) (Box 11)
    - FAE35 Ways to Justice (Goldsmidt, Walter and Sinclair, Lester), 1954-1955 (Box 11)
    - FAE36 Looking at Modern Paintings: A Discussion Leader's Guide (The Fund for Adult Education), 1958 (Box 11)
    - FAE37 Residential Colleges: Some New Developments in British Adult Education (Hunter, Guy) (Box 11)
    - FAE37A Looking at Modern Paintings (Freedman, Leonard), 1961 (Box 11)
    - FAE38 Education: The Challenge Ahead (Fletcher, C. Scott) (Box 11)
    - FAE39 The Perkins Lectures: Popular Government and Foreign Policy (Perkins, Dexter), 1956 (Box 11)
    - FAE40 Ways of Mankind: How to organize a listen-and-talk group in your own home, 1960 (Box 11)
    - FAE40A Exploring the Ways of Mankind (Goldschmidt, Walter), 1961 (Box 11)
    - FAE40B Discussion Leader's Guide for Use with Exploring the Ways of Mankind (Goldschmidt, Walter), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE40C Ways of Mankind: An Adult Discussion Program (Goldschmidt, Walter), 1955 (Box 11)
    - FAE40D Ways of Mankind (National Association of Educational Broadcasters), 1958 (Box 11)
    - FAE40E The Ways of Mankind: A Discussion Leader's Guide (The Fund for Adult Education), 1953 (Box 11)
    - FAE40F A Word in Your Ear: A Study in Language (Essay No. 1 in the series of experimental discussion programs on "The Ways of Mankind"), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE40G The Ways of Mankind Adult Discussion Series: How People Live Together Different Times and Places (The Fund for Adult Education), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE40H Ways of Mankind Discussion Leader's Guide, 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE41 You and Modern Art (Langsher, Jules), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE42 The Citizen and the Mass Media (Dale, Edgar and Kilbourn, Robert W.), 1956 (Box 11)
    - FAE43 You and the Mass Media Part I; Supplementary readings; Part II; Additional readings to Session III (Seldes, Gilbert), 1957 (Box 11)
    - FAE44 [MISSING] You and Your Community (Box 11)
    - FAE44A Our Community (Mial, Dorothy and Curtis), 1980 (Box 11)
    - FAE44B Obstacles to Healthy Community Growth (Dodson, Dart W.), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE44C The Future of the Community (McKee, Elmore), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE44D Participant's Manual (Fund for Adult Education), 1954 (Box 11)
    - FAE44E Aging in the Modern (World University of Michigan), 1957 (Box 11)
    - FAE45 Shakespeare and His Theatre (Canadian Association for Adult Education), 1958 (Box 12)
    - FAE46 The Power to Govern (Odegard, Peter H. and Rosenblum, Walter G.), 1956 (Box 12)
    - FAE47 Transition and Tension in Southeast Asia (Peffer, Nathanial), 1957 (Box 12)
    - FAE48 You and Modern Art (Fund for Adult Education), 1953 (Box 12)
  - Library of Continuing Education at Syracuse University series (LCE)
    - LCE1 Directory of Adult Education Association (Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1965 (Box 12)
    - LCE2 Directory of Adult Education Association (DeCrow, Roger; Ironside, Diana J.; Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1966 (Box 12)
    - LCE3 University Adult Education: A Selected Bibliography (DeCrow, Roger; Ironside, Diana J.; Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1966 (Box 12)
    - LCE4 Directory of Adult Education Association (Ironside, Diana J.), 1968 (Box 12)
    - LCE5 Directory of Adult Education Organizations (Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1970 (Box 12)
    - LCE6 [MISSING] Recent Acquisitions: Adult Education Periodical Holdings and Adult Education Newsletter Holdings (DeCrow, Roger; Ironside, Diana J.; Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1971 (Box 12)
    - LCE7 [MISSING] International Seminar on Adult Education (Ziegler, Warren L., Seminar Director) (Box 12)
  - Landmark and New Horizons series (LNH)
    - LNH1 Report on the 1969 Galaxy Conference of Adult Education Organizations (Charters, Alexander N.), 1971 (Box 12)
    - LNH2 The Cooperative Extension Service: Paradoxical Servant (Miller, Paul A.), 1973 (Box 12)
      See also Drafts, notes and galleys: LNH2 The Cooperative Extension Service: Paradoxical Servant
    - LNH3 A Tale of Three Cities: Elsinore-Montreal-Tokyo (Kidd, James Robbins), 1974 (Box 12)
    - LNH4 The Worker's Educational Association: Aims and Achievements (Fieldhouse, Roger), 1977 (Box 12)
  - Manuscript series (MSS)
    Many of the MSS documents have been digitized and are available online. To view these document, please click here.
    - MSS1 Aids to Access - Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N.), 1978 (Box 12)
    - MSS2 Professional Development of Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS3 Desarrollo Professional de Educadores de Adultos (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS4 Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1978 (Box 12)
    - MSS5 Who We Are: What Some Educators Say About Their Characteristics, Competencies, and Roles (Charters, Alexander N. and Hilton, Ronald J.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS6 Continuing Education for Educators of Adults: The Roles of Research (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS7 Syracuse University Resources in Adult Education (Charters, Alexander N.), 1978 (Box 12)
    - MSS8 Periodicals, Newsletters, & Indexes in E.S. Bird Library and Clearinghouse of Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald P.), 1978 (Box 12)
    - MSS9 Accessibility to Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS10 Acquisition List Pamphlet File - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N.), 1977 (Box 12)
    - MSS11 Abstracts of Dissertations and Theses: Syracuse University Graduates in Adult Education (Charters, Alexander N.), 1979 (Box 12)
    - MSS12 Publications in Continuing Education, Revised (Charters, Alexander N.), 1980 (Box 13)
    - MSS13 Acquisition List Pamphlet File - E.S. Bird Library - Revised (Charters, Alexander N.), 1980 (Box 13)
    - MSS14 Clearinghouse Resources for Educators of Adults. Four Year Report October1975-June 1979) (Charters, Alexander N., Project Director), 1980 (Box 13)
    - MSS15 Syracuse University Resources in Adult Education, Revised (Charters, Alexander N.), 1979 (Box 13)
    - MSS16 Adult and Continuing Education Collections: A Descriptive List of Manuscript Holdings in Syracuse University Libraries (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1977 (Box 13)
    - MSS17 Adult Education Masters' Theses and Doctoral Dissertations on Microfilm in S.U. Library (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1977 (Box 13)
    - MSS18 International Handbook of Resources for Educators of Adults (Charters, Alexander N., ed.), 1979; 2 versions, 6.76 and 10.76 (Box 13)
      See also related collection
      Alexander Charters Papers: Professional correspondence-subject files: International Handbook of Resources for Educators of Adults
      .
    - MSS19 Personal Papers of Frank C. Laubach: Documents of Laubach Literacy, Inc. (Chmaj, Deborah R. and Wolde, Menbere, compilers), 1974 (Box 13)
    - MSS20 The Paul Hoy Helms Library in Liberal Adult Education (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1973 (Box 13)
    - MSS21 The What and the How of the Syracuse Collection (Stubblefield, Harold), 1984 (Box 13)
      In some lists, MSS21 is given as "Omnibus Series (Charters, Alexander N.), 1965." However, that is not what is in the collection.
    - MSS22 Audio Tapes - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1976 (Box 13)
    - MSS23 Adult Education Sound and Video Recordings - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N. and Abbott, George), 1982 (Box 13)
    - MSS24 Omnibus Series - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1976 (Box 13)
    - MSS25 Humanizing Adult Education Research: Five Stories from the 1930's (Hilton, Ronald), 1982 (Box 13)
    - MSS26 Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald), 1983 (Box 13)
    - MSS27 Syracuse University Publications in Continuing Education on Microfiche (Charters, Alexander N.), 1983; See MSS36 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS28 [MISSING] Continuing Education Photograph Collection: by Event and Person (Charters, Alexander N. and Davis, Carolyn) (Box 13)
    - MSS29 Adult Education Periodicals and Newsletters - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N. and Gschwender, Edward), 1983; See MSS41 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS30 [MISSING] Acquisition List Pamphlet File - E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N. and Goodman, Edward), 1983 (Box 13)
    - MSS31 SUPCE and SUREA: Publications and Resources for Educators of Adults (Stubblefield, Harold W.), 1983 Nov (Box 13)
    - MSS32 Syracuse University Resources for Educators of Adults A Retrospective View: Looking into the Future (Charters, Alexander N. and Vaughn, Betty Jane), 1986 Jan; See MSS53 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS33 Historical and Research Materials Related to Adult Continuing Education (Frost, Jane B., compiler), 1988; See MSS35 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS34 The Adult Education Collection at Syracuse University (Charters, Alexander N., compiler), 1989 (Box 13)
    - MSS35 Historical and Research Materials Related to Adult Continuing Education (Frost, Jane B., compiler), 1992; Revision/update of MSS33 (Box 13)
    - MSS36 Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald), 1992; Revision/update of MSS27. See MSS45 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS37 Adult Education Sound & Video Recordings (Charters, Alexander N. and Abbot, George), 1992; Revised and updated MSS23. See MSS48 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS38 Bibliography of Materials Autographed by Educators of Adults, 1992 (Box 13)
    - MSS39 Finding Aid to Alexander N. Charters Materials in Archives (Charters, Alexander N.), 1992 (Box 13)
    - MSS40 Abridged Descriptive Subject Listing for Adult and Continuing Education Research Collection, 1992 (Box 13)
    - MSS41 [MISSING] Adult Education Periodicals and Newsletters – E.S. Bird Library., 1992; Revision/update of MSS29 (Box 13)
    - MSS42 Adult Education Acquisitions List: Pamphlet File, E.S. Bird Library (Charters, Alexander N.), 1992; Revision/update of MSS30 (Box 13)
    - MSS43 Some Observations: Early Years of Committee/Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) (Charters, Alexander N.), 1992 (Box 13)
    - MSS44 Comparative Studies in Adult Education: A Review (Charters, Alexander N.), 1992 (Box 13)
    - MSS45 [MISSING] Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N. and Holmwood, Donald), 1996; Revision of MSS36. See MSS49 for later version. (Box 13)
    - MSS46 Photographs in Adult and Continuing Education (A); Descriptive Subject Headings (N) (Charters, Alexander N.), 1995 (Box 13)
    - MSS47 SUPCE Supplements to MS 13, 29, 35, 37, 38 (Charters, Alexander N. and Keenan, Terrance), 1995 (Box 13)
    - MSS48 Adult Education Sound and Video Recordings (Charters, Alexander N. and Abbot, George), 2003; Revision/update of MSS37 (Box 13)
    - MSS49 Publications in Continuing Education (Charters, Alexander N. and Shablak, Scott), 2003; Revision/update of MSS45 (Box 13)
    - MSS50 Adult Educational Journals and Associations (Charters, Alexander N. and Shablak, Scott), 2003 (Box 13)
    - MSS51 Adult and Continuing Education Pamphlets, Materials and Fugitive (Charters, Alexander N.), 2004 (Mar) (Box 14)
    - MSS52 Syracuse University Adult and Continuing Education: Pamphlets, Materials and Fugitive (Shablak, Scott and Cooper, Natasha), 2004 (Aug) (Box 14)
    - MSS53 Syracuse University Resources for Educators of Adults: A Retrospective View: Looking into the Future (Charters, Alexander N. and Shablak, Scott), 2006; Revision/update of MSS32 (Box 14)
    - MSS54 Continuing Education at Syracuse University, 1973 (Charters, Alexander N.), 2005 (May) (Box 14)
    - MSS55 Comparative Adult Education: An Overview (Charters, Alexander N.), 1988; 2007,; 2008 (Box 14)
  - Notes and Essays in Continuing Education for Adults series (NES)
    - NES1 The Pooling of Ignorance (Smith, Russell F.W.), 1952 (Box 14)
    - NES2 Report to Atlanta Convention (CSLEA), 1952 (Box 14)
    - NES3 Evaluating Courses not Students (Miller, Harry L.), 1953 (Box 14)
    - NES4 Social Roles of the Middle-Aged (Havighurst, Robert), 1953 (Box 14)
    - NES5 Television and the University (University of Chicago), 1953 (Box 14)
    - NES6 A School for Optimists (McGee, Paul), 1953 (Box 14)
    - NES7 The Liberation of the Adult (Kallen, Horace), 1954 (Box 14)
    - NES8 Adult Education as a Time-Binding (Hayakawa, S. I.), 1954 (Box 14)
    - NES9 Mass Society and Liberal Education (Mills, C. Wright), 1954 (Box 14)
    - NES10 Teaching a Human Relations (Malumud, Daniel I.), 1955 (Box 14)
    - NES11 Faculty Organization at Rutgers (Demarest, G. Stuart), 1955 (Box 14)
    - NES12 Psychological Needs for Adults (Murphy, Gardner and Kuhlen, Raymond G.), 1955 (Box 14)
    - NES13 Schooling for Maturity (Diekhoff, John S.), 1955 (Box 14)
    - NES14 The Residential School in American (Pitkin, Royce S.), 1956 (Box 14)
    - NES15 Professional Preparation of Adult Educators, 1956 (Box 14)
    - NES16 Reality and Purpose: A Visitor's Reflections on Some Aspects of American Adult Education (Elsdon, Konrad. T.), 1957 (Box 14)
    - NES17 Adult Education in the Liberal Arts Colleges (Crimi, James E.), 1957 (Box 14)
    - NES18 Liberal Education (Carnegie Foundation), 1957 (Box 14)
    - NES19 Especially for, Adults (Whipple, John B.), 1957 (Box 14)
    - NES20 The Marginality of Adult Education (Clark, Burton R.), 1958 (Box 14)
    - NES21 I Want Many Lodestars (Schwertman, John B.), 1958 (Box 14)
    - NES22 Learning and Teaching Through Discussion (Hill, Ida Stewart and Hill, William Fawcett), 1958 (Box 14)
    - NES23 Pleasures in Learning (Division of General Education of New York University), 1958 (Box 14)
    - NES24 Major Trends in Higher Adult Education (Houle, Cyril O.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES25 Liberal Education for Adults Re-Examined: The Queens College Program (Belth, Marc and Scheuler, Herbert), 1959 (Box 14)
    - NES26 Higher Adult Education: Its Place and Function (Simons, Hans), 1959 (Box 14)
    - NES27 A Report on University Adult Education in Australia and New Zealand (Sheats, Paul H.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES28 Aims in Adult Education: A Realist View (Broudy, Harry S.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES29 Week-End Learning in the USA (Schacht, Robert H.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES30 Adult Education in Colleges and Universities, Liberal Adult Education (Liveright, A. A. and Miller, Harry L.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES31 Adult Education in the British West Indies (Houle, Cyril O.), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES32 On Teaching Adults: An Anthology (Miller, Marilyn V., editor), 1960 (Box 14)
    - NES33 People, Programs, and Persuasion: Some Remarks About Promoting University Adult Education (Stern, Milton R.), 1961 (Box 14)
    - NES34 Today and Tomorrow: Three Essays on Adult Education in the Future (Taylor, G.; Blackwell, G. W.; Mead, Margaret), 1961 (Box 14)
    - NES35 Challenge to the University: An Inquiry into the University's Responsibility for Adult Education (Burch, Glen), 1961 (Box 14)
    - NES36 The University and Community Education (Haygood, Kenneth), 1962 (Box 14)
    - NES37 Educational Imperative: The Negro in the Changing South (Goldman, Freda H.), 1963 (Box 14)
    - NES38 The Few and the Many: Two Views on Public Affairs Education (Freedman, Leonard and Power, Hilton), 1963 (Box 14)
    - NES39 Meanings of Work (Levy, Sidney J.), 1963 (Box 14)
    - NES40 Psychological Backgrounds of Adult Education (Kuhlen, Raymond C., editor), 1963 (Box 14)
    - NES41 Sociological Backgrounds of Adult Education (Burns, Hobart W., editor), 1964 (Box 14)
    - NES42 Ordered Pluralism: A Philosophical Plan of Action for Teaching (Barton, George E.) (Box 14)